groundreport.com 2009-06-17

# Hyperlocal News & Opinion Around the World | GroundReport

**Privacy Policy**

Ground Report LLC ("GroundReport", "we," or "us") is committed to ensuring the privacy of our users. This Privacy Policy ("Policy") describes how personal information is collected from users of the GroundReport's Web site located at www.groundreport.com ("Site"), and how that information is used and disclosed. By using our Site, you consent to the terms of this Policy.

**Personal Information**

Personal information is information that specifically identifies an individual, such as a user's name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card or other account number, and information about that individual's activities when directly linked to that person such as information about his or her purchases or use of services. Personal information also includes demographic information such as date of birth, gender, geographic area and preferences when such information is linked to other personal information that identifies you.

**Personal Information We Collect**

You provide personal information to us in a number of ways when you visit our Site or use the various services and activities available on our Site. For example, you provide us with personal information when you: (1) register an account on the Site; (2) post an article or comment to the Site and voluntarily include your name or other personal information (including, without limitation, any personally identifying photographs or images you submit/post); or (5)contact us by email for any reason (such as to request customer service or provide us with your comments/feedback). We collect your name and email address in this manner. If you request or apply for compensation from us for your articles, comments or other submissions to the Site, we will collect certain additional personal and demographic information from you (including, without limitation, your full legal name, address and PayPal address).

When you visit our Site, some information is also automatically collected, such as your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, operating system and browser type and the time and date of your visit. This information is collected through the use of "cookies." Cookies are small files that are stored on your computer by a Web site to give you a unique identification. We also use cookies on our Site to to record your user preferences and to keep you logged into the Site. We treat automatically collected information as personal information if we combine it with or link it to any of the personally identifying information mentioned above. Otherwise, it is used in the aggregate only.

We may use third parties, called third-party ad servers or network advertisers, to deliver ads to you on our behalf. These third-party ad servers may use cookies, Web beacons or other technology to collect non-personally identifiable information about your visits to our Site in order to use it to present advertisements that may be of interest to you.

**How We Use the Information We Collect**

In general, we use personal information to process your requests or transactions, provide you with services, and present you with relevant advertisements. For example, we use the information we collect to:

  * contact you for administrative purposes or provide you with customer service;
  * complete transactions requested by you or to verify that you have submitted an article or comment;
  * respond to any questions, problems or complaints, or request feedback;
  * organize the Site and its various services and activities to better serve you and customize or develop our products and services; and
  * present you with relevant advertisements based on your anonymized information.

**Disclosure of Information**

We do not sell, rent or share personal information with third parties without your prior consent except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy. We share personal information with third-party vendors who assist us in performing internal functions necessary to operate our business. These functions may include, for example, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and processing payment transactions. In all cases we limit the information shared with our third-party vendors to that which is necessary to carry out those functions. We are not responsible for any information you provide to these parties directly, and we encourage you to become familiar with their practices before disclosing information directly to them.

We also disclose personal information when we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law (e.g., a lawful subpoena, warrant or court order); to enforce or apply this Policy or our other policies or agreements; to initiate, render, bill and collect for amounts owed to us; to protect our or our users' rights, property or safety; to protect our users from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of, our Site; or if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay.

In addition, information about our users, including personally identifiable information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing or sale of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personally identifiable information could be transferred to third parties as one of our business assets.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

Our Site contains links to other Web sites. Links from our Site to other sites or content are provided for your convenience only, and we do not have control over the content or privacy and security practices and policies of such third parties or other sites. Any personal information you provide on linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party's privacy policy. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information.

**Choice and Access**

To opt-out of receiving communications from us, or to request access to or that we correct or delete your personal information, please email us at info@GroundReport.com.

Please note that opting out of receiving communications from us will not prevent you from receiving administrative communications, such as those concerning the operation of the Site or about an article or comment you have submitted.

**Children**

We do not intend, and the Site is not designed, to collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13 years old, you should not register with or otherwise provide personal information to our Site.

**Security**

We use reasonable security measures in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. We cannot, however, guarantee protection of all information against interception, misappropriation, misuse, or alteration, or that your information may be not be disclosed or accessed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others. Furthermore, we have no control over the security of other sites you might visit, interact with or do business with.

Your registration information is accessible online only through the use of a password. To protect the confidentiality of personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of the Site by any person using your password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your password has been misused or otherwise misappropriated.

**Policy Changes**

We will modify this Policy if our privacy practices materially change in the future. We will notify you of such changes only by posting the new policy on our Site and indicating at the top of the Policy the date it was last updated. We encourage you to review the Policy each time you visit our Site to see if it has been updated since your last visit to make sure you understand how personal information you provide will be used.

**Questions / Additional Information**

If you have any questions about this Policy, or the practices of or your dealings with the Site, please email us at info@groundreport.com.

**Terms of Use**

GroundReport is an open news platform for original content. GroundReport will under no circumstances tolerate the publication of false, obscene, hateful or unauthorized content. 

To report obscenity, false information or hate language in text and/or images, please use the _Report Abuse_ button on the relevant article page. If unable to use the "Report Abuse" function, please use the [Contact Form](http://www.groundreport.com/info.php?action=contact) and specify the article in violation.   

GroundReport respects the Digital Millenium Copyright Act (DMCA) and its application for a designated agent is pending. In the interim, please use the [Contact Form](http://www.groundreport.com/info.php?action=contact) for all copyright complaints. GroundReport takes copyright infringement seriously and responds promptly to all complaints.   

**Writers**

Writers on GroundReport implicitly agree to publish only truthful, original text and images in their articles. Violation of copyright or publication of libelous, obscene and/or hateful language will result in deletion of all articles and account termination.

**Writers will not profit from the publication of false or unauthorized text or images.** Writers forfeit all earnings associated with false or unauthorized content.   

Writers retain all rights to and ownership of the articles they write on GroundReport. In publishing their work on GroundReport, writers agree to allow the publication of their article and images on [http://www.groundreport.com](http://www.groundreport.com/) alongside contextual advertisements. Upon publication, writers have the option to select from the following licenses to protect their work:

_**Attribution (Very Relaxed)**_  
  
---  
  
Allows for changes and redistribution, commercial and non-commercial, that credits you as author.

|   
_****__**Attribution No Derivatives (Relaxed)**_  
  
Allows for redistribution, commercial and non-commercial, that credits you as author. No changes to your work are allowed.  
  
_****__**Attribution Non-commercial (Strict)**_  
  
Lets others redistribute, change and build upon your work non-commercially.  
  
_****__**Attribution Non-commercial No Derivatives (Very Strict)**_  
  
Allows for non-commercial redistribution that credits you as author. No changes to your work are allowed.  
  
**Readers**

Readers agree to respect the intellectual property licenses associated with images and text on GroundReport.com. 

**Comments**

GroundReport does not tolerate the posting of spam or hate language in comment fields. Comments containing advertisements, profanity, obscenity or hate language will be promptly deleted and the commentor's account terminated.
